<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on Geoff Tuttle</title>
    <link>https://www.geofftuttle.com/tags/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on Geoff Tuttle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.geofftuttle.com/tags/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MPCNC</title>
      <link>https://www.geofftuttle.com/projects/mpcnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 23:18:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geofftuttle.com/projects/mpcnc/</guid>
      <description>The Mostly Printed CNC (MPCNC) is an entry level DIY kit for a small CNC milling machine developed by Ryan at V1Engineering. This well-documented project is supported by a huge community of tinkerers, hobbyists, and professional machinists who have contributed a multitude of add-ons to the machine.
This is a record of work performed and milestones reached on building my own MPCNC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Part Mold Making</title>
      <link>https://www.geofftuttle.com/blog/two-part-mold-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geofftuttle.com/blog/two-part-mold-making/</guid>
      <description>Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to take a 3d printed tabletop miniature and replicate it with a two part mold. This will speed of production of a part that would normally take two to three hours, and give us the freedom of different materials and colors.
Two part molds allow us to cast more complex shapes than a one part, or open-face, mold. This open face creates a flat surface on the piece we are making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Needle Cutter Rebuild</title>
      <link>https://www.geofftuttle.com/projects/mpcnc/needle-cutter-rebuild/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 16:36:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geofftuttle.com/projects/mpcnc/needle-cutter-rebuild/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a hiatus, I decided to revisit the needle cutter and get back to making planes from the free svg plans on FliteTest. I wanted to characterize the performance of the MPCNC and develop a streamlined workflow for creating parts that would fit together snug without being too tight.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
